and Lenin began to lay down, uh, these
а Ленин начал закладывать ээ вот эти
republics to invent, he also invented the
республики придумывать он же придумал
Ukrainians, he invented the Belarusians, but there was no
украинцев придумал белорусов да не было
Belarus, yes, he invented Belarus, there will be a
ж Белоруссии да он придумал Беларусь
Belarusian Soviet
будет белорусская Советская
Socialist Republic, he invented Kazakhstan, he invented
Социалистическая Республика придумал
there, it was called
Казахстан придумал там назвал
Kirghizskazskaya, the USSR was first
Киргизсказская СССР сначала называлась
called, but then it was called Kazakh, so he
да потом уже казахской её назвали вот
invented there, Turkmenistan, this
попридумывал там Туркменистан этот
Tajikistan, Kyrgyzstan, under the Russian
Таджикистан Кыргызстан при Российская
Empire, all this was Western Turkestan, it was
империя это всё был западный Туркестан
called
называлось
good evening, good evening, I am from the city of
добрый вечер добрый я из города
Khmelnitsky, where are you from,
Хмельницкий вы откуда
Roston, and how do you communicate, yes, in
ростон а чём общаетесь
different ways,
да по-разному
for example,
например
well, it depends more on the interlocutor, it's
ну как от собеседника больше зависит
funny, what do you think, why are our
прикольно как считаете почему у нас
fraternal Slavic peoples
братские славянские народы
fighting, what are you talking about now, well,
воюют вы сейчас о чём
Russians, Ukrainians, we are one people, yes,
ну русские украинцы мы же один народ да
well, that means there is a civil war, Putin
ну значит идёт гражданская война путин
started a civil war, well,
начал гражданскую войну
because Ukraine took the
ну потому что Украина стала на стороне
wrong side, it took an
неправильной она взя заняла позицию
anti-Russian position, well, why is this happening, because of
антироссия да ну почему получается это
what, because you yourself
из-за чего потому что вы же сами
understand that in 1991,
понимаете что в девяносто первом году
Yeltsin and Gorbachev sold the Soviet Union to the
Ельцин и Горбачёв продали Советский Союз
Americans, and Gorbachev withdrew his troops  from
американцам да горбачёв вывел войска из
East Germany in eighty-nine they
Восточной Германии в восемьдесят девятом
tore down the Berlin Wall then they withdrew
развалили берлинскую стену потом вывели
from, uh, Poland, Czechoslovakia, Hungary, the countries of the
из ээ Польши Чехословакии Венгрии стран
Volshavsky Treaty, yes, they left there
Волшавского договора да они ушли оттуда
after that, Yelny, drunk, in short, took it and
после этого Ельн пьяный короче взял
signed it together with Shushkevich and our
подписал вместе с Шушкевичем и нашим
Kravchuk, they were drinking in the Belvezhskaya Pushcha,
этим Кравчуком Белвежской пущи бухали
and then in the morning they took it and painted it, in
они там а потом утром взяли намалевали
short, the Soviet Union no longer exists and that's it, the
что короче Советского Союза больше нет и
Americans immediately came in and
всё американцы сразу зашли да под
took control of all 15 republics, including the
контроль взяли все 15 республик включая
Russian Federation, put
Российскую Федерацию поставили вам этих
all these banker advisers in your place, and so on,
всех советников банкиров и так дальше да
and we have, that is, the American occupation of
и у нас то есть американская оккупация
our lands has been going on since ninety-one,
наших земель идёт с девяносто первого
and instead of taking and
года и вы вместо того чтобы взять
launching three liberation nut trees
запустить три орешника освободительных
on London, Berlin, and
на Лондон на Берлин и на
Washington and liberating the fraternal
Вашингтон и освободить братский
Slavic people who are hostage to the
славянский народ который в заложниках у
Americans, you took us, attacked
американцев вы взяли напали и убиваете
us, and are killing us, and the Americans are rubbing their hands, the Americans are
нас а американцы потирают ручки
not dying, the Russians
американцы не погибают погибают русские
and Ukrainians are dying, that is, the Slavs, the Americans
и украинцы то есть славяне американцы
are implementing the Dalis plan, yes, to
реализовывают план Далиса да по
liberate the territory from the Slavic
высвобождению территории от славянского
population, yes, a
населения да
great idea, just
прекрасная мысль вот дайте
wait  and why have we
как подожди а почему к этому сейчас
come to this only now we haven't
пришли только раньше об этом не
thought about it before
задумывались в смысле у нас давно про
I mean we've been talking about this for a long time I remember I was at
это говорит я ещё ээ помню я был в
university in 1998 I
университете в девяносто восьмом году
entered university in my second year I
поступил в университет на втором курсе
was in the Eurasian Circle we discussed
был в Евразийском кружке мы разбирали
these issues yes that it was as if we needed to do
эти моменты да что как бы нужно делать
some kind of anti-NATO anti-American propaganda
антиамериканскую какую-то пропаганду
because uh the collapse of the Soviet Union the
потому что ээ развал Советского Союза
defeat of the Soviet Union in the
проигрыш Советского Союза Союза в
Cold War gave us these consequences and
холодной войне дал нам эти последствия и
Russia is also under occupation
Россия тоже находится под оккупацию у
you still have this Elvira Nabiullina
вас до сих пор вот эта Эльвира Набиулина
judging by your good past words we
судя по вашему хорошо прошлым словам нам
need to unite now and fight back
нужно сейчас объединиться и дать отпор
America like this or how we can't look
Америки так или как мы не можем смотрите
we can't unite because we are
мы не можем объединиться потому что мы
now under occupation yes it's like for
сейчас под оккупацией да это как
example uh we are West Germany we are
например вот ээ мы Западная Германия мы
now under occupation and you are East yes
сейчас под оккупацией а вы восточная да
you are the Soviet Union all your year
вы вот Советский Союз все свою году
thank you and we are now under the American
спасибо а мы сейчас по под американской
we are under the Americans and you are under the American too yes you are under the
мы под американс а вы под тоже да вы под
American and
американской и
Yes and for some reason when Putin yes I
Да и почему-то вот когда Путин да я
thought that he would take and he would strike at
думал что он возьмёт и он сделает удар
Berlin strike at Washington and London
по Берлину удар по Вашингтону и Лондону
as the center of decision-making  Anglo-Saxon and
как центр принятия решения англосакса а
he climbed in and you know what the worst thing is that
он полез и знаете что самое страшное что
we have a lot of people who were like
у нас очень много людей которые были как
me who said that yes, Russia is a friend and
я которые говорили что да Россия друг и
we need it, we need it, yes, we are one people,
нам нужно нам нам нужно да мы один народ
we must, in short, reunite the Soviet
мы должны короче воссоединить Советский
Union, our grandfathers fought, and now Russia is
Союз наши деды воевали а теперь Россия
throwing missiles at these cities and people
кидает ракеты на эти города и люди
say: "What kind of friend is she to us?"   You
говорят: "А какой она нам друг?"
see, how can I explain to people
Понимаете как вот мне объяснить людям
that Russia is a friend
что Россия - это друг
why now Russia is now under whose
почим сейчас Россия сейчас под чьей
occupation is it under the American under the American
оккупации находится под американской под
and the Americans rule and
американской и американцы управляют да
you and us are ruled by the Americans and
и вами и нами управляют американцы да и
what do the Americans do look if
американцы что делают смотри если бы
Russia were not ruled by the Americans
Россия не управлялась американцами
Russia was fighting against America now and
Россия воевала против Америки сейчас а
Russia is fighting against the brotherly
Россия воюет против братского
Slavic people which the Americans are
славянского народа который американцы
using as pawns that's all
используют как пешки вот и всё
Russia is now being used by the Americans as a
россию сейчас используют американцы как
pawn no the Americans are using Russia and
пешку нет американцы используют Россию и
Ukraine as pawns killing the Slavic
Украину как пешек убивая славянский
people both from the territory of Russia and from the
народ как с территории России так с
territory of Ukraine well and how did it
территории Украины
all start - let's
ну а с чего всё началось-то давай
try to figure it out that is to say I'm
попытаемся разобраться то есть я же
telling you it all started in
говорю всё началось с восемьдесят
1989 when the Berlin
девятого года когда опала берлинская
Wall fell Gorbachev we didn't want Wait in
стена горбачёв мы же не хотели Подожди в
1989 we didn't want to
восемдесят девятом году-то мы не хотели
kill the Ukrainians right that's not
убивать украинцев правильно же так не
right I'm telling you look the
так я же тебе говорю смотри пала
Berlin Wall fell and the
берлинская стена да вывели из стран
Soviet troops were withdrawn from the Warsaw Pact countries and
Варшавского договора советские войска да
all 15 republics were given to the Americans well
отдали американцам все 15 республик ну
Gorbachev and Yeltsin came up with it they
Горбачёв с Ельциным это ж придумали
gave it  and it turns out that the Americans
отдали и всё и получается что американцы
immediately introduced their systems of governance
сразу внедрили свои системы управления
and their advisers their people to all
да своих советников своих людей на все
posts in the republics I understand correctly I
посты в республиках правильно понимаю я
understand correctly Putin Putin is now
правильно понимаю путиным Путиным сейчас
ruled by the Americans yes yes that's also absolutely
рулит американцы да да тоже абсолютно
right let's
верно
say that not even the Americans Anglo-Saxons
скажем так даже не американцы англосаксы
because Trump is also controlled by the
потому что Трампом тоже крутят
Anglo-Saxons you understand that the main
англосаксы вы же понимаете что основая
system of world governance is not
система мирового управления находится не
in the USA
в США
the USA is just used by the world globalists
сша просто у мировых глобалистов
as you know a dog
используются как такой знаете
cerberus the world policeman yes when it is
пёсцербер мировой полицейский да когда
necessary to punish someone who went
нужно наказывать каких-то кто пошёл
against world globalism for example
против мирового глобализма например
Saddam Hussein yes when it is necessary
Саддама Хусейна да когда нужно
Milosevic well when Putin went or did not
Милошевича ну когда Путин пошёл или не
go against it no Putin did not go
пошёл против этого нет Путин не пошёл
there look if Putin went against
есть смотри если бы Путин пошёл против
uh globalism yes then the world
ээ глобализма да тогда бы э мировое
community would have already bombed Moscow yes and
сообщество уже бы бомбило Москву да а
so they are like so it doesn't bomb
так они типа так она короче не бомбит
it's just like that uh despises there
она просто такой как это э презирает там
and look it is beneficial for world globalism
и смотрите мировому глобализму
Anglo-Saxons British crown that
англосаксам британской корони выгодно
Russia somewhere there in the nameless
чтобы Россия где-то там в безымяных
gullies of Donbass kills its own
балках Донбасса убивала своё население
male population and kills Ukrainians that is
мужское и убивало украинцев то есть
Slavs yes  the thing is that maybe you
славяне да дело в том что может вы
know there is such a project New Khazaria
знаете есть такой проект Новая Хазария
yes when on the territory of this is just
да когда на территории вот это как раз
Don Rostov Kuban Donetsk region
Дона Ростова Кубании Донецкой области
Lugansk region Kharkov a
Луганской области Харьковская должна
new Khazaria should be created where in case of an
быть создана новая хазария куда в случае
escalation in the Middle East the
обострения на Ближнем Востоке должны
Israelis should be resettled
быть переселены израильтяне
where did you read that mm where did you
где вы прочитали такое мм где это вы
read that look yes there is a magazine of the
прочитали посмотрите да есть журнал
Belgian Club published every
Бельдербергского клуба выходит каждый
year yes reports yes in Yorkshire they
год да сводки да вот в Йоркшере они в
gather in Yorkshire once a year sirs like yes
Йоркшере собираются раз в год сэры такие
they are like the British elite and
да они вроде как британская элита и
they got in yes and listen yes listen no
они попали да и послушают да послуша нет
so they publish their they publish
так они же публикуют свои они публикуют
their their magazine yes well let's say the topic as I
свои свой журнал да ну скажем тема я так
understand it interests yes interests well I Yes
понимаю интересует да интересует ну я Да
look the thing is that I am from the time of the
смотри дело в том что я из ещё со времён
Eurasian circle and I am interested in
евразийского кружка и я интересуюсь
all these societies and that is why are
всеми этими обществами вот и это почему
you interested well
вас интересует
why such societies yes
ну почему такие общества да потому
because I understand that world
потому что я понимаю что на мировую
politics is influenced not by some elections not by
политику влияют не какие-то выборы не
some but by these secret ones well ska they are
какие-то а вот эти тайные ну ска они уже
no longer secret even yes it is possible there are
они не тайные даже да это возможно есть
some other secret ones  societies that
ещё какие-то тайные общества про которые
we don't know about and these are far from secret
мы не знаем а это далеко не тайные
societies that is to say there is the British
общества то есть есть британская
aristocracy they left the monarchy and
аристократия они же оставили монархию
made themselves a fake parliament yes
сделали себе фейковый парламент да там
let's change it today there will be Tories
давайте мы поменяем сегодня будет Тори
tomorrow there will be Liberals yes but all
завтра будут либористы да вот но всё
the same everything is decided by the Vinzer family so well the
равно всё решает семейство винзеров так
main thing is that you are in the know and know all this yes I
ну главное что вы в теме и всё это
know and I preach
знаете да знаю и проповедую
perfectly the
прекрасно
question: how can we stop the
вопрос: как нам остановить
fratricidal war of Slavs with
братоубийственную войну славян со
Slavs and strike at the Anglos
славянами и ударить по англосам
Maidan arrange another Maidan and no well
майдан устройте ещё один майдан а не ну
we don't look what Maidan we are not
мы не смотри какой майдан мы же не
arranging an anti-Maidan do you believe that
устраиваем антимайдан ты ты веришь что
you believe that some people came out
ты веришь что тут какие-то люди выходили
to Maidan these were British
на Майдан это были британские
instructors American instructors no no
инструкторы американские инструкторы нет
it wasn't I came and looked at
нет это не было я приезжал смотрел на
this Maidan yes there were people there
этот Майдан да там были по-английски
speaking English yes like they
разговаривали да типа с британскими
spoke English with the British what well all
разговаривали по-английски что ну все
my Donetsk people who were there on the
мои дончане которые там находились на
square are not those who were shown to you on
площади не те кого вам показывали по
TV yes there were hired actors yes and
телевизору да были нанятые актёры да а
so they walked yes instructors Mishest so do
так ходили да инструктора Мишесть так
n't tell all this fables
что это всё не рассказывайте басни
Krylova the thing is that you believe that
Крылова дело в том что вы верите что
people can change something where was it in the
народ что-то может изменить где было в
world for people to change something
мире чтобы народ что-то изменил
so you changed everything there so no one
так вы же там всё поменяли так никто не
changed you were shown a picture and they
поменял тебе картинку показали и нам
showed us a picture everyone: "Oh Maidan Maidan" they
картинку показали все: "О Майдан Майдан"
really just made this picture but it
реально сделали просто картиночку эту а
turns out that you have this somehow not like
получается у вас вот это как-то не то
you have Maidan the scheme of
что как у вас там Майдан схема
independence here all this or what
незалежность вот эта вся всё это что ли
in the sense of what independence if we are
в смысле какая независимость если мы
dependent on America and the Anglo-Saxons since
зависимы от Америки и англосаксов с
ninety-one we have well there was
девяносто первого года у нас ну вот было
this slogan after Maidan what was yours
этот лозунг после Майдана как ваш там
called
назывался
it all this in general what slogan what
он всё это вообще какой лозунг какой
I don't
я уже не
remember what it was called exactly remember well
помню как он назывался точно вспомни ну
this whole idea of Maidan it all or what
вся эта идея Майдана она всех что ли что
or
или
how well you all stood up there against the
как ну вы там встали все против
state
государства
against Yanukovych all this or what
против Януковича всё это или что это
was it well it's a
было
lie or what was it a
это ложь или что это было
deception I'm not very interested in
обман я политикой не сильно интересуюсь
local politics because in fact there is none
местной потому что её фактически нет
local but be interested in foreign politics well
местной а чужой интересуйся да ну потому
because in Ukraine and in Russia there is no politics yes
что в Украине и в России нет политики да
because there are no decision-making centers
потому что нету центров принятия решений
yes there are only  the protgs of the Anglo-Saxons,
да есть только ставленники англосаксов
in Britain there is politics, yes, in
вот в Британии есть политика да в
Britain there is an aristocracy, it makes
Британии аристократия она принимает
decisions, look, if you have
решение вот посмотри если у вас есть
politics, why haven't you been
политика почему у вас до сих пор не
able to remove Elvira
могут снять Эльвиру
Nabiullina yet, such is the head of your Central Bank,
Набиулину такая глава Центробанка ваша
and what's wrong with her? And what's wrong with her? Well, she is a
и что с ней не так м А что с ней не так
protg of world globalism,
ну она ставленница мирового глобализма
it is she who is raising the key rate for you, yes,
это же она вам повышает ключевую ставку
she introduced the dollar, all the evil comes from her, yes, no, not
да она внедряла доллар всё зло от неё да
from her, from the Anglo-Saxons,
да не не от неё от англосаксов
but she, as a protg of the Anglo-Saxons, yes, she is
но она как ставленник англосаксов да
creating an obstacle for us here so that we can
создаёт нам тут препятствие чтобы мы
develop further, that's
развивались дальше
interesting, and also all these
вот это интересно так са также эти все
Chubais, Zhirinovskys, and so on, well, you are from
Чубайсы Жириновские и так дальше ну
there, from Ukraine, that's better known, as I
вам-то оттуда с Украины-то это виднее я
understand it, I am not from Ukraine, and where are you from?
так понимаю я не из Украины а откуда ты
I am originally from Rostov, but I
будешь я самродом из Ростова но живу
now live in Poland,
сейчас в Польше
from Rostov, yes, Rostov the Great, and
с Ростова да росто который великий
where were you born, in Rostov the Great? And
а где ты родился в Ростове Великом м а
where are you in Rostov the Great? I was not born in Rostov the Great, well, I
где ты в Ростове Великом я не не в
just
Ростове Великом родился ну только что
said that I am from Rostov the Great,
сказал что Ростове Великом я из Ростова
but I was not born in  Rostov you will tell me
но не родился в Ростове ты же скажешь
where you were born I was born in Yaroslavl
где родился родился я в Ярославле
I understand and now I understand
я понял ну а сейчасста я так понимаю
Ukraine is behind you there is no Ukraine I am in
Украина у тебя сзади поч Украи нет я в
Poland my friends from the Russian
Польше это мне друзья из русского
volunteer corps sent me this
добровольческого корпуса выслали
[music] I
[музыка]
understand a gift
понятно подарок
yes they are fighting against the Kremlin junta yes I am
да они воюют против Кремлёвской хунты да
proud
горжусь
and why are you proud of this look if
а почему ты гордишься этим смотри если
we are under the Americans why did you unhook it
мы под американцами все зачем ты отцепил
because well look this is a prince this is the sign of
потому что ну смотри это князь это знак
Prince Vladimir who baptized Rus this is the
князя Владимира который крестил Русь это
trident of Prince Vladimir I studied yes
ж тризуб князя Владимира я изучал да
Vladimir is just from the time when we were
Владимир как раз времён когда мы были
one people when Vladimir baptized Rus and
один народ когда Владимир крестил Русь и
we were all Orthodox
все мы были православными
yes I understand the flag has to do with it because this is
да понятно флаг здесь причё потому что
Harugva of the Galicia-Volyn
так это Харугва Галицко-Волинского
principality of Russian yes Danila
княжества русского дазь Данила
Romanovich the Grand Duke King of Rus
Романович великий князь король Руси
wait now what Prince Danila
подожди сейчас какой князь данила
Romanovich who is called Danila
Романович которого называют Данила
Galitsky he is the Russian king said that the
Галицкий он король русский сказал что
cross Vladimir is his attribute there
крест Владимир это его там атрибут там
his flag is there yes this is not Prince
флаг его да это это не это князя
Vladimir's attribute but the
Владимира атрибут а
flag of the king let's talk about the flag
флаг короля про флаг говори мы про флаг
and  what does kres Vladimir have to do with the flag
а причём здесь крес Владимир про флаг
they talked about it in general in my opinion kres
говорили он вообще по-моему кресть
Vladimir so the flag is also on our
Владимир так флаг - это тоже на наш
Slavic flag and your Slavic flag well
славянский флаг а ваш славянский флаг да
well the king of Rus yes the king of Rus Danila
ну король Руси да король Руси Данила
Romanovich like this flag had the king of
Романович типа флаг этот имел король
Rus
Руси
look Rex Ruthenia yes it was called
посмотри Рекс Рутения да назывался
when your king of Rus was there then the
когда там был твой король Руси значит
kingdom was so I understand correctly it
королевство было так правильно понимаю
was the kingdom of Rus or what in Rus
было королевство Рус или что в Руси ну
well google google king of Rus Danila
загугли загугли король Руси Данила
Romanovich will you tell me
Романович будет ты мне расскажи
interesting see he was first the prince of the
интересно видишь он был сначала князем
Galicia-Volyn principality yes and then
Галицко-Волинского княжества да а потом
like took the title of king of Rus yes and who is the
типа принял титуль король Руси да а кто
corval pope pope
корвал папа римский папа римский
carnival on the throne king of Rus yes are
карнавал на трон король Руси да ты
you serious look rex Rutania it
серьёзно ты ж посмотри рекс Рутания
was called he had the title yes why should I
назывался он титул имел да зачем мне это
look at this well what and what are you so tired of this at all and who are you who
смотреть ну а что а во приедел вообще
look let's start
это а ты кто ты кто смотри давай начнём
look who are you nationally you are not Russian
смотри кто ты по националь ты не русский
you are not a Slav so who am I well you are
ты не славянин так а кто я ну ты
some kind of Tatar because you are
какой-то татарин потому что ты вот
against  Slavs, too, I see, and who
против славян тоже смотрю вижу а кто
told you that I am against Slavs, well, and what
тебе сказал что я против славян ну а кто
nationality are you, that you started coughing already,
ты по национальности что закашлялся уже
and when did the truth begin, Russian, what kind of Russian are you, pore tykiy and
а когда правда начало русский какой ты
not Russian, look,
русский пору тыкий а не русский посмотри
what kind of Russian are you, the real one,
какой ты русский
born in Kharkov, you hear, born in Kharkov, a real
слышишь родился в Харькове настоящий
Russian, born well, you are Tatars, you are Khazars, and
русский родился ну так ты татари ты
what about Kharkov, Tatarzhu, well, Kharkiv
а что в Харькове татаржу ну харь Харьков
is a Turkic city,
- это тюркский город
and a wild field was
да дикое поле было
Polovtsian, Polovtsian
половц половецкий
degree, and there, besides the Tatars, someone else
степень а там ещё кроме татар ещё кто-то
lived there, probably Russians too, Berendeys,
жил же наверное же русский тоже берендеи
Pechenegs, well
печенеги
there, and Ukrainians lived, no, Ukrainians
ну там А украинцы жили нет украинцы
in general, Lenin invented it after the revolution,
вообще Ленин придумал в после революции
Ukrainians did not exist, such people, that's
украинцев не существовало таких
good, you
вот это хорошо ты
said Lenin invented it because
сказал Ленин придумал потому что Ленин
Lenin was an agent of German intelligence,
Ленин же был агентом немецкой разведки
yes, when my grandfather was born in Kharkov, he also did
да мой дед когда родился в Харькове тоже
not understand that there were Ukrainians there, yes, my
не понял что там были украинцы да да мой
grandfather, oh, not my grandfather, I gozhu Lenin when he
мой дед ой не мой дед гожу Ленин когда
arrived in Russia after the
приехал в Россию после революции
February Revolution, yes, in a sealed carriage, you
февральской да в опломбированном вагоне
know, this is Lenin's carriage, and then what happened when he
знаете это ленинский вагон да дальше что
arrived and started on  let's say money from
приехал и начал на скажем деньги
German intelligence to do subversive
немецкой разведки делать подрывную
activities and they made the Great
деятельность и сделали Великий
October, so the October Maidan, yes,
Октябрьский так октябрьский майдан да
first there was the February Maidan, which
сначала был февральский майдан который
Kerinsky made, yes, they overthrew the tsar, and they
сделал Керинский да свергнули царя а и
made a provisional government, and then
сделали временное правительство а потом
Lenin made this October Maidan, he
Ленин сделал этот Октябрьский майдан
overthrew the provisional government of
свёр свергнул временное правительство
Kerinsky, and then he shot the tsar, the
Керинско а потом ещё расстрелял царя
legitimate tsar, the blood tsar, yes, that
законного царя кровненького царя да то
is, the Romanovs, and what do we see, yes, what do
есть Романовых и что мы что мы видим да
Yeltsin, oh, not Yeltsin, but Lenin, began to
что Ельцин ой не Ельцин а Ленин начал
lay down these republics, to come up with, he also came up with the
закладывать вот эти республики придумать
Ukrainians, he came up with the
он же придумал украинцев придумал
Belarusians, but there was no Belarus, yes, he came up with Belarus, there
белорусов да не было же Белоруссии да он
will be a Belarusian
придумал Беларусь будет белорусская
Soviet Socialist Republic, he came up with Kazakhstan, he came up with it, he called it Kirghiz, the
Советская социалистическая республика
USSR was first called, and
Киргизская СССР сначала называлась да
then they called it Kazakh, yeah, yeah, he
потом уже казахской её назвали вот угу
came up with it, there Turkmenistan, this
попридумывал там Туркменистан этот
Tajikistan, Kyrgyzstan, under the Russian
Таджикистан Кыргызстан при Российская
Empire, it was all Western Turkistan, it was
империя это всё был Западный Туркистан
called, and all this used to be, all the
называлось и всё это раньше была всё
Russian Empire, that's right, all the
Российская империя правильно всё
Russian Empire was, yes, from
Российская империя была да вот от
Vladivostok, in short, to Finland, you
Владивостока короче до Финляндии
understand, and Lenin came and  said: "All
понимаешь а пришёл Ленин и сказал: "Всё
this is no longer the Russian Empire, I am
это больше не Российская империя я
now divided into nationalities" so that's
делюсь сейчас на национальности" так вот
how it happens yes yes Lenin is simply a
так бывает да да ленин - это просто
traitor to the Russian people, simply a
предатель русского народа просто
traitor, he himself was
предатель он сам был по национальности
half Chuvash and half Khazar by nationality yes
наполовину Чуваш наполовину Хазарин да
this Jew yes no
этот еврей
German no so he lived there in
да на немец нет так он жил там в в
Germany in Switzerland there for money in short
Германии в Швейцарии там за бабки короче
his sponsors yes these came began to
своих спонсоров да эти приехал начал
destroy the foundations immediately against
разваливать устои сразу против
Orthodoxy against the churches his these
православия против церквей его эти
girlfriends and they already had yes also the same thing
подружки а у них уже было да так же то
happened yes this one they also then
же было да вот этот у них же потом вот
this Rosa Luxemburg and this Alexandra
это Роза Люксембург и это Александра
Kalantay these two girlfriends yes who
Калантай две этих подружечки да которые
walked hand in hand they made this
за ручку ходили они ж сделали этот
feminist congress
феминистический съезд
and decided that there should be a revolution,
и постановили что должна быть революция
that a Komsomol member should give a Komsomol member a
что комсомолка должна дать комсомольцу
glass of water to drink so they destroyed the
как стакан воды выпить вот развалили
churches our priests were repressed well well
церкви наши батюшек порепрессировали ну
what about yours I don't understand kvasses you do
ну что ж вашек я не пойму квашек ты
n't understand at all where you came from are you
вообще не пойму откуда ты взялся ты
now somewhere in Poland in Poland you
сейчас там где-то в Польше в Польше ты
are there well I'm Russian your
находишься тамще ну я русский ваше
churches and  some religion is like
церкви а какой-то религия вообще такой
that Poland is also Poland is our
так Польша - это тоже польша - это наши
brothers Slavs
братья славяне
who told you that operation Slavs
кто тебе такое сказал операция славяне
Polish Poles Slavs we are all brothers
поль поляки славяне мы все братья
Slavs Croats Croats Serbs Czechs
славяне хорваты хорваты сербы чехи
Poles wait about the Serbs Salash
поляки подожди поводу сербов салашу по
about the Poles not yet we look we
поводу поляк не още мы смотри мы вместе
fought together with the Poles against Hitler yes who are you who are you
с поляками против Гитлера воевали да кто
here we are with the fields yes we are with the
вы кто вы вот мы с полями да мы с
Poles the battle of Grunwald the Germans
поляками битва при Грюнвальде немцев
were restored in short we
восстанавливали короче мы в битве под
became Mongolians in the battle of Legnica with the Poles I
легницей монголос становили с поляками я
understand you perfectly I
тебя понял прекрасно я себя
identify myself as Russian you as who how do
идентифицирую как русский ты как кто как
you identify yourself yes what kind of Russian are you well
тебя идентифицируе да какой ты русский
look you are really some kind of either
ну посмотри ты реально какой-то либо
Tatar or Armenian what kind of Russian are you well
татарин либо армянин какой ты русский ну
wait here we are who someone okay I am a
подожди вот мы кто кто-то ладно я
Slav well where are you from Well
славянин
what nationality are you
ну а ты отку Ну какой ты национальность
I am a Slav nationality Lenin
я славяни национальности Ленин
invented before Lenin we were all Slavs
придумал до Ленина мы все были славяне
Orthodox Slavs
православные славяне
so Poles are not Orthodox some Poles are
так поляки не православные часть поляков
Orthodox and so what but most are not so
православный и что а большинство нет ну
what well they are all  equally brothers Slavs we are
и что ну они всё равно братья славяне мы
all Slavs we came from the clan of Svorog
все славяне мы пошли от рода сворога
Perun you know
Перуна понимаешь
wait what are they brothers we were all
подожди чего они на братья мы все были
Slavs brothers Slavs we are not Germans we are not
славяне братья славяне мы не германцы мы
Turks we are Slavs who said who is the number such thing there is
не тюрки мы славяне кто сказал кто числ
such a movement
такое есть такое почитай течение
is called pan-Slovism we all Slavs
называется пансловизм мы все славяне
should unite and give the Anglo-Saxons
должны объединиться и дать англосаксов
constantly fought with the Poles the Poles were
постоянно с поляками воевали поляков
constantly divided tell me not the Poles
постоянно делили расскажи не поляки
always in short they wanted to free
всегда короче они хотели освободить
Moscow from the Tatar-Mongol yoke because
Москву от татаро-монгольского ига потому
when the Tatar-Mongols captured yes
что когда татаро-монголы захватили да
Moscow gave trouble every year all the
Москву даили беда каждый год всех
girls and men like in Moscow the Poles
девушек и мужиков типа в Москве поляки
yes said that it is necessary to stop this let's
да говорили что нужно прекратить это
say mockery of the Russian people
скажем издевательство над русским людом
and the Russian people resisted and said:
а русский люд сопротивлялся и говорил:
"No let the Tatars-Mongols
"Нет пусть на татарамонголы
liberate us or no the Poles did not
так освободили или нет нас поляки не
liberate us" so to this day you
освободили" так до сих пор вас
Tatars-Mongols this Kadyrov in short bends
татары-монголы вон этот Кадыров короче
you all
вас всех нагинает
naked descendant of Chegiskhan yes well yes and you
нагихам потомок Чегисхана да ну да и ты
here  look a little if you speak
вот немно посмотри если ты говоришь
Russian you have really
русский у тебя ну реально
Genghis Khan expressions epicanthus
чигисханские выражения лица эпикантусы
narrow eyes bro unibrow I just I
узкие глаза бро монобровь я просто я
just haven't slept for 2 days that's why I'm so
просто 2 дня не спал поэтому такой
tired haven't slept for 2 days I understand yes that is
уставший 2 дня не спал понял да то есть
you are also tired heir of Genghis Khan well you
ты ещё уставший наследник Чингисхана
see so we basically and we
ну вот видишь так что мы в принципе и мы
Poles are for returning our
поляки за то чтобы вернуть наш
pan-Slavic union Poles yes
панславянский союз поляки да
and you yourself it seems like already well I understand correctly
а ты сам походу уже ну правильно понимаю
you are no longer Orthodox you are already a Catholic I do
ты уже не православный ты уже католик я
n't I don't believe at all I am an atheist well well
не я вообще не верю я атеист
you had parents they
а ну у тебя родители же были они тебя
baptized you no I have Soviet
крестили нет у меня же советские
parents they were in the Soviet Union atheism
родители они в Советском Союзе атеизм
was and in the Soviet Union they weren't baptized yes
был а в Советском Союзе не крестили да
no in the Soviet Union churches were
нет в Советском Союзе церкви были
banned we were enlightened like
запрещены мы были просвещённые типа
Soviet people we uh all Soviet
советские люди мы ээ все советские
Slavs we are not religious Slavs
славяне мы не религиозные славяне
what is this story well look we have
что вот эта история ну посмотри у нас
such a feeling as if we served in different
такое ощщение как будто мы в разных
unions oh well wait look
союзах служили ой ну подожди посмотри
since the time of our this great
ещё со времён нашего этого великого
Russian commander  Joseph Visarionovich
русского полководца Иосифа Висарионовича
Dzhugashvili yeah
Джугашвили угу
churches were closed and because well they were
церкви были закрыты и потому что ну они
unnecessary well and why for example
за ненадобностью ну а зачем вот например
in our area from a church they made a
у нас на районе из из церкви сделали
store warehouse
магазин склад
so yeah it's like that of course you weren't
так что да это такое вас конечно не
baptized at all yours was baptized and where were you
крестили вообще ваш крестили а тебя что
baptized where could you be baptized
где-то крестили где тебя могли крестить
in Kharkov I was born in Kharkov what
в Харькеве я же родился в Харкове какой
year was your birth
какой год рождения
seventy eight where were you
семьдесят восьмой где ты в семьдесят
baptized in Kharkov in seventy eight what do you
восьмом в Харькове покрестился что ты
think
придумаешь
where is Chugulsky rav yeah there
ты где чугульского раве угу там циркушка
was a circus yes yes there was a church what are you
была дада церкушка была что ты
talking about only KGB officers could be
рассказываешь там только кгбшники могли
these clergymen there it's clear well
быть этими церковнослужителями понятное
yeah what difference does it make maybe he
дело ну да какая разница может быть у
had this like KGB officer's badge I don't
него и был этот как корочка кгбшика
care he already baptized me with a cross and
мне-то всё равно он уже меня крестом а
not a badge what did
не корочкой крестил
he tap you with something soft
чем он тебя там постукал чем-то мягким
on the forehead and dipped me in this dipped and in
по лбу да окунул меня в этот окунул а в
his liquid understood candle sacred
жидкости свои понял свещ свещённая
sacred
свещённая
water understood listen and what
водичка понял слушай а какие ты можешь
Slavic peoples can you name can you name that
назвать можешь назвать славянские народы
you  you know
которые ты знаешь
peoples yes
народы да
Ukrainians Russians Belarusians Serbs Greeks
украинцы русские белорусы
Greeks
греки
yes they are Slavs
да они славяне
you And now wait Slavic no I I
ты А сейчас подожди славянские нет я Я
thought
думал
Orthodox and who else do you have
православные а кто у вас ещё
there everything in my opinion finish your
там всё по-моему закончить свои
knowledge of Slavic Orthodox and
познания славянских православных а
wait well damn Georgians don't fit they are
подожди ну блин грузины не подходят они
not Slavs they are just Orthodox
у нас не славяне они просто православные
then which of the Slavs do you
то кого из славян ты
know this I just indicated well
знаешь это я только что обозначил ну
name Ukrainian Russians Belarusians and that's it and Serbs
назови украинский русские белорусы и всё
so and Czechs words Czechoslovaks well
и сербы так а а чехи слова чехисловаки
maybe yes some of them are also
ну может быть да часть из них тоже
Orthodox and Croats
православных а хорваты
Croats in my opinion they are no longer Slavs I
хорваты по-моему они не уже не славяне
will not argue I don't know and Slavs
не буду спорить я не в курсе а славян
maybe Slavs
может бы славяни
I don't know I won't tell you and
я не знаю не буду тебе говорить а
Montenegrins here to lie I won't lie and
черногорцы вот врать врать не буду а
Macedonians and Bulgarians Bulgarians
македонцы а болгары
Slavs and Upper Sorbian Serbs and
болгары славяне а верхнелужецкие сербы а
Lower Sorbian Serbs yes I don't understand so much I understood
нижнелужецкие сербы да я так сильно не
these understand then you I
разбираюсь понял вот эти поня то ты Я
understood because you are not you are not a Slav  you
понял потому что ты не ты не славянин
see you are not a Slav you do not know
понимаешь ты не славянин ты не знаешь о
anything about the Slavs yes I am just Orthodox
славянах ничего да я просто православный
and that's it and
и всё
who listen well okay if not
да а кто слушай ну хорошо если не
Slavs and who is needed definitely not a Pole and definitely
славяни а кто нуж точно не поляк и точно
not a Catholic definitely not a Pole you are not a Slav
не католик точно не поляк ты не славянин
because the Poles with these who who
потому что поляки с эти
fields Slavs Slavs And you are not
кто кто поля славяне славяне А ты не
Slavs they saw well I say that you are
славянни они видели ну я говорю что ты
not a Slav because the Poles are not like
не славянин потому что поляки не такие
you
как ты
okay well why are they different from me from
о'кей ну чего они отличаются от меня
you they have intellectual faces
от тебя интеллектуальные лица у них
like yours yeah I
как у тебя угу
understand you can't tell me and a Pole apart we are
понятно вот меня и поляка не отличишь мы
intellectually educated everyone listen you
интеллектуально образованы каждо слушай
see every Pole and you are amazed that is a
каждого поляка видишь и поражаешься вот
real intellectual that's how I just
это реально интеллектуал вот как просто
want listen
хочется слышь картины писать
I want to paint pictures of every Pole and of someone like
хочется с каждого поляка и с такого как
you against the background of the Ukrainian flag I just
ты на фоне украинского флага вот просто
want to sketch you like you how do you
хочется зарисовать вас как ты как ты
think like why did you
считаешь типа почему вот вы
Tatar-Mongols become
татаро-монголы стали
so unhappy after the capture of Moscow
такими несчастными после захвата Москвы
who captured you I don't know what you are
кто вас захватил я не знаю о чём ты
talking about if no one captured me well
говоришь если меня никто не захватывал
I don't remember that you understand I don't remember that
ну я не помню этого понимаешь не помню
I  someone some Tatars
чтобы меня кто-то какие-то татары
Mongols captured
монголы захватывали
here you are Tatars-Mongols
вот ты татары-монголи
okay in short that's it come on Genghis Khan
ладно короче всё давай чингисханец
so the mouse I'll run
так-то мышь я побегу
and we will liberate Moscow we the Slavs will
а мы освободим Москву мы славяне
liberate Moscow and the RDK will take it
освободим Москву и РДК возьмёт её
let's like this like subscribe komen
давай вот так лайк подписка комен
subscribe to my Instagram I don't know
підпишись на мій Instagram я не знаю для
why you are there for what else you are there
чого це тобі для чого ще тобі там
marvel at Ostaf ale for you there are one
дивитись на Остафе але для тебе це один
two or three clicks ale you support me
два або три клика але ти підтримаєш мене
and I will say: Wow, I have a lot of
и я буду казати: "Вау в мене там купа
followers there and I will be great,
фоловерів и в мене буде класний
tune in to my Instagram pop Andrey
настроись на мій Instagram попик Андрей"
so let me tickle you
отакчик давай я тебя очекаю